txu.com 2011-04-26

# TXU Energy Privacy Policy

This Website is owned by Energy Future Holdings. ("

TXU Energy

"). We know that many visitors to our site are concerned about the information they may provide and how we may use that information, so the following is provided to address those concerns. If you have questions about our Website Privacy and Policy, you may e-mail us at [Corp.Comm@txu.com](mailto:Corp.Comm@txu.com) or write to: 

Energy Future Holdings.  
Energy Plaza  
1601 Bryan St., Suite 34-068  
Dallas, TX 75201  
Attn: Corporate Communications 

**Our Policy**  
Except as otherwise provided in this Policy, 

TXU Energy

 does not collect personally identifiable information from individuals unless they provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. We only collect personal information for specific purposes such as responding to requests for information or to provide services. We will not sell or provide your information to unaffiliated companies for commercial purposes unrelated to the business of 

TXU Energy

. In some instances, we may use this information to inform you of goods and services that may be of interest to you. Except as provided herein, 

TXU Energy

will not disclose any information about you to unaffiliated companies or organizations without your consent, unless: 

  * required by law; 
  * we believe it necessary to respond to an inquiry or provide you with a service which you have requested; 
  * to implement our terms of service; 
  * to protect the rights, property or personal safety of another TXU Energy user, any member of the public or TXU Energy.

TXU Energy and its affiliates recognize the trust you place in us when you give us personal information. In order to operate the Website or deliver a service we may sometimes share your personal information with a service partner under strict conditions. We will not otherwise disclose your personal information to other companies without your explicit consent. TXU Energy reserves right to change Website Privacy Policies at any time, and will immediately post the updated information on its Website. 

You are not required to register or provide information to us in order to view much of our site. To obtain services from TXU Energy or subscribe to certain portions of our Website, such as, but not limited to, the TXU Energy "Small Business Portal" or other services provided by TXU Energy , you may be asked for personal information. We use your information to personalize your Web experience or to provide the services you requested. TXU Energy will only use your information strictly in accordance with this Policy. 

**Access to Your Information**   
If at any time you want to know exactly what personal information we hold about you or wish to change personal information that is inaccurate or out of date, please contact us by e-mail at [custinfo@txu.com](mailto:custinfo@txu.com) and we will amend this record. 

**Security  
** TXU Energy will endeavour to take all steps deemed reasonable by TXU Energy to keep secure any information we hold about you, and to keep this information accurate and up-to-date. Your information is stored on secure servers that are protected in controlled facilities. We require our employees and data processors to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by TXU Energy . Unfortunately, no data can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot give an absolute assurance that the information you provide to us will be secure at all times. TXU Energy will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorized access to your personal information. 

TXU Energy may use overseas facilities to process or back-up information. As a result, we transfer and store your personal information in our overseas facilities. However, this does not change any of our commitments to safeguard your privacy. 

**Viruses**   
TXU Energy uses appropriate commercially available anti-virus software to ensure that this Website does not contain or carry viruses. However, due to the rapidly developing nature of viruses and the Internet we strongly recommend that you employ similar anti-virus software when accessing the TXU Energy Website. TXU Energy makes no warranty that the Website or e-mail correspondence is free from such viruses. 

**Cookies and Other Information**   
Like many companies, we may from time to time use "cookie" technology on our Website. "Cookies" are small text files a Website can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and to track usage behavior of, for example, the Web pages you visit. Our Website may automatically collect Cookies and other information, such as, but not limited to, your domain name and Internet protocol address, and compile aggregate data for statistical purposes to improve our content and services and administer our Website. 

**Privacy Protection for Children Using the Internet**   
Our Website contains energy-related information that may be of educational interest to children. TXU Energy does not seek to gather personal information online from or about children under the age of 13. TXU Energy encourages all children and young teens to always seek consent from their parents before providing any information about themselves or their household to ANYONE on the Internet.
